So in our previous video, we have seen how to crack Mifare classic card using default keys.
In this video we are going to see what if we have modified all the keys and we have just kept one key
in a default format or in a transport configuration?
Are we still able to do the same attacks or not?
This is what we are going to see in this video.
So let's just find out the Uid of this card first.
So we have to type Xf as before.
And if you don't remember all the commands, all you can do is type Xf and then over here it will display
the next commands which you can use with Xf.
So what I have to use is F 14 A and then I have to read.
So it will display the Uid.
Right.
So this is the Uid of this card.
Now let's just type f and f for mifare.
And we want to check the block keys of this card.
So to check the block keys for this card, you have to type K to check.
And again, we have to do this check command on all sectors.
So I'll type star then.
This is A1K card.
So I'll type one and then I'll type question mark because I don't know any keys as of now.
And then what I have to do is I have to transfer all the keys in our emulator memory.
Which is the memory of Proxmox.
So let's just hit enter.
And over here you can see all the keys are unknown.
In fact, in all the sectors like key, as are all the keys are unknown and all the key B's are also
unknown except the key key B in sector four.
So key B in sector four is known and all the other keys are unknown.
So now what we are going to do is we are going to perform the same nested attack on this card as well
and try to find all the other keys using this one default key.
So let's just do a nested.
And we are going to do the attack on one card and we don't know anything about this card.
So we'll type star.
And then what we have to do is we have to type T to transfer.
All data.
Into our emulator memory.
Let's just hit Enter.
And over here you can see it has start finding the valid keys.
So it might take a few minutes or a few seconds to find all the keys.
Okay.
So as you can see, it's taking some time, but it's finding the valid keys.
All right, so all the valid keys are found.
Just by using this one default key.
Right.
So you can see all the key A's and key B's are also available now just by using this one default key.
So if by mistake, you have kept only one key, whether it's Key A or key B in the card in a default
format, this card will still be vulnerable to this type of attacks.
Right.
So this is what I wanted to show you.
So now I can read any block from any sectors.
There are commands, as you can see over here.
If I type F and there are commands to, you know, write block and read, block or read sector, I can
read Complete Sector.
Just by using this one default key, we were able to find all the other keys.
So the point of this exercise was to show you that you should modify all the sector trailers, whether
you are using those sector trailers or not.
So over here, by mistake, if you have left only one key or more than one key in a default format,
that card will still be vulnerable to such type of attack.
And in the next video we are going to see.
Whether we are able to do same attacks.
If we have modified all the keys on all the sectors and we will see all those attacks on on another
card in which we have modified all the key A's and B's of all the sectors.